[
    {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Who invented Java language?",
    "a": "Dennis Ritchie",
    "b": "James Gosling",
    "c": "Larry Page",
    "d": "Serge Page",
    "answer": "b"
},
{
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What is an Interpreter?",
    "a": "An interpreter converts instructions line by line",
    "b": "An Interpreter converts source code to low-level code",
    "c": "Interpreters are slow to execute",
    "d": "All the above",
    "answer": "d"
},

{
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What is the file name extension of a Java source program?",
    "a": ".j",
    "b": ".ja",
    "c": ".java",
    "d": ".jax",
    "answer": "c"
},
{
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Byte code is the result of?",
    "a": "Compiling a Java file",
    "b": "Compiling a Class file",
    "c": "Interpreting a Java File",
    "d": "Interpreting a Class file",
    "answer": "a"
},
{
    "id": 5,
    "question": " What software compiles a Java Program?",
    "a": "JRE (Java Runtime Environment)",
    "b": "JDK (Java Developer Kit)",
    "c": "JVM (Java Virtual Machine)",
    "d": "Command Prompt",
    "answer": "b"
},
{
    "id": 6,
    "question": "In which of the following is toString() method defined?",
    "a": "java.lang.Object",
    "b": "java.lang.String",
    "c": "java.lang.util",
    "d": "None",
    "answer": "a"
},
{
    "id": 7,
    "question": "When is the object created with new keyword?",
    "a": "At Runtime",
    "b": "At Compile time",
    "c": "Depends on the Code",
    "d": "None",
    "answer": "a"
},
{
    "id": 8,
    "question": " What software compiles a Java Program?",
    "a": "JRE (Java Runtime Environment)",
    "b": "JDK (Java Developer Kit)",
    "c": "JVM (Java Virtual Machine)",
    "d": "Command Prompt",
    "answer": "b"
}
,
{
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Arrays in java are-",
    "a": "Objects References",
    "b": "Objects",
    "c": "Primitive Data Type",
    "d": "None",
    "answer": "b"
},
{
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Number of primitive data types in Java are?",
    "a": "6",
    "b": "7",
    "c": "8",
    "d": "9",
    "answer": "c"
}


]